

PROFIL

Hello and welcome to my Curriculum Vitae. My name is Faddoul El-Achkar Raed, I was born the 10/11/1999 and I have just finished my third year at UFRA specializina in computer (ESGI). I am engineering hardworking and very curious. I will undoubtedly ask you a thousand and one questions, but it is to quench my thirst for learning. I intend to become a great developer!

CONTACT

GitHub: gitRaed

E-MAIL:

raedfaddoul@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Faddoul Raed

HOBBIES

Video games Reading learning

FADDOUL EL-ACHKAR RAED

Full stack software engineer

EDUCATION

2017: baccalaureate at ILE, Abidjan, Ivory Coast

2017-2018 : first year at l'Université Française d'Abidjan (UFRA), ESGI (Ecole Supérieure de Génie Informatique)

2018-2019: second year at l'UFRA, ESGI

2019-2020: third year at l'**UFRA**, **ESGI**, got ESGI's bachelor + FreeCodeCamp JavaScript algorithms and data structures certification

2020: FreeCodeCamp Front end Libraries certification

EXPERIENCE

01/07/2019 - 31/08/2019: internship in the research & development team of Ab Soft Work

03/02/2020 – 04/05/2020: internship in the research & development team of Ab Soft Work, I created pickseat there!

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Bootstrap
- Sass
- JavaScript
- Angular
- React
- Node.is
- Leaflet.is
- Git GitHub : basicsMicrosoft flow : basics
- SQL: basicsAgile method